fasapay.com 2019-02-05

# Privacy Policy - FasaPay Online Payment System

Privacy Policy of FasaPay is determined by Fasa Centra Solutions Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as "FasaPay") regarding to collection, usage of, and disclosure of personal information that obtained by FasaPay Members (hereinafter referred to as "FasaPay Member"). This Privacy Policy applies to all services that available on FasaPay application and/or website. FasaPay Member is expected to read this privacy policy properly and carefully so that FasaPay Member can understand how FasaPay uses your personal data as a FasaPay Member. 

By giving your personal data and/or personal information in access fasapay.com (hereinafter referred to as "FasaPay website") then you have understand how personal data and/or personal information you have given will be used. 

By using FasaPay services, you are agree to be bound with the Privacy Policy along with the Terms and Conditions of FasaPay. 

## User Identity

When registering to FasaPay service, FasaPay Member will be required to fill data completely and correctly (valid) regarding, including no exception, among others: full name, address, date of birth, phone number, handphone number, email address and/or website address, bank account number, and name of the bank account owner, and other data that is deemed necessary by FasaPay. 

Regarding verification and validation data process, FasaPay Member must upload scan of identity card in the form of DRIVER LICENSE or INTERNATIONAL PASSPORT. To upgrade membership status, FasaPay Member must upload scan of billing statement in the form of electricity, water, telephone, cable TV, internet, gas, or credit card bill at least the last three months and obliged to be sent in English language format also legalized by local authorities. 

FasaPay Member with Company or Store status must upload domicile letter of business license or residence domicile along with company legality (if any) authorized by local functionary for futher verification process. 

FasaPay Member will be asked by FasaPay to collect identification information from FasaPay Member in many ways, not limited to, when FasaPay Member access menu of FasaPay application and/or website, make transactions and payments, activities, services, and/or other features that available on FasaPay application and/or website. 

This personal data of FasaPay Member will be collected by FasaPay as administration data and to support us prevent any money laundry and terrorism funding activity. FasaPay is not allowed and not entitled to abuse its personal data for any commercial interests of FasaPay and/or other interests that can disadvantageous FasaPay Member. 

## The Purpose of Data Collection

Your personal information provided to FasaPay is useful for us so that we can give the needed services and information better. If you have agreed the purpose of data collection to support our service, you have the right to change your mind anytime, but this will not influence any process that have occurred. We use your information because we have legitimate interest to do, and you have the right to refuse data collection, in some cases, this may mean that you are no longer using FasaPay services, and for that, we use your personal information to: 

  1. Improve the customer service where information from FasaPay Member help FasaPay to respond the service requests and support needs of FasaPay Member more efectively.
  2. Answer questions and/or requests you are submitted. 
  3. Send any service notification and give customer support. 
  4. Anticipate and solve problems, detect and prevent any fraud related to products we offer. 
  5. Verify identity, audits, and for obedience purpose towards government regulatory standards. 
  6. Monitoring the transactions conducted with FasaPay and/or FasaPay’s merchants. 
  7. Record all information from your computer and browser, including IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you requested. 
  8. Manage or perform our obligations associated with any Agreement between you and FasaPay. 

## Cookie

Cookie is file stored inside computer, including smartphone, tablet, or any device you use. Its file used to load simple data about your habit when using browser application. Cookies help your browser to browse websites and the cookies themselves will not collect any information that stored on your computer. Cookies work to remember important information that will help in the use of sites, in case the visitor decides to revisit the site in the future. 

FasaPay uses cookies for session login, save CSFR token, and visitor tracking on live chat of FasaPay Member in the use of FasaPay service. You can choose to set up computer, smartphone, tablet, or other devices to refuse cookies or provide warnings when cookie is sent. 

## Confidentiality and Security

FasaPay applies technology and collection data policy, storage, appropriate processing practices, and security measures in accordance with applicable rules in Malaysia with the purpose of protecting your privacy against unauthorized access, improper use, destruction, disclosure, information loss, or your personal identity theft, transaction information, and data that stored on FasaPay. 

There is no data transmission through internet or website that guaranteed securely from any interference. But, we always keep the sensitive and personal data exchange between FasaPay host and FasaPay Member is going through SSL secure track also encrypted and protected with digital signature. 

All information you have given to us are stored in our server or our service provider and can only accessed also used in accordance with our policies and security standard. Where we have gave you (or where you have decided) password and/or PIN that make you possible to access parts of FasaPay website, you are liable to keep the password and/or PIN confidentiality and obey another security procedures we have told to you. We will update this steps along with new technology development according to the needs. 

## Data Change

FasaPay applies policy of personal data verification by admin before the data is changed. FasaPay party is entitled to accept or refuse the submitted personal data change depends on the change and FasaPay is entitled to ask for the proof of submitted change, as long as the proof is true and appropriate so then personal data of FasaPay Member can be changed. 

## Newsletter

We will ask for your approval before use your personal information for this matter. If you choose to not receive the newsletter, you are entitled to refuse and delete your name and/or personal information form newsletter’s list. If you are disposed to choose yes to receive our marketing information from us then we are entitled to send you information or communication associated with FasaPay services, like announcement service, administration message, and FasaPay newspaper that is rated as part of FasaPay product marketing. This is not including the communication about security PIN that we send to you when using our services. 

## Information Disclosure

Personal data information obtained by FasaPay from FasaPay Member will be saved for a certain period time. FasaPay will not sell, exchange, or send any information provided by FasaPay Member to any unauthorized third parties. FasaPay can deliver information obtained by FasaPay Member, including but not limited to, among others: 

  * If ordered by law and/or request from authorities, central banks, or other finansial institutions.
  * Fulfill the compliance to the constitution, the litigation, or the law.
  * Protecting against unauthorized use or abuse of FasaPay menu application.

FasaPay Member hereby release and waive FasaPay from all demands, claims, indemnity, court fees, and/or lawsuits regarding to granting access to the information. 

## Changes Against Policy and Privacy

FasaPay is entitled and can change also update the Privacy Policy and/or our Cookie policy. We can change our website content and how we use the cookies, and as the result this Privacy Policy can change anytime without prior notification. If we change or update our privacy policy, we will inform the change of policy through email and/or on FasaPay website and you are expected to keep update this privacy policy.

## Closing

By using FasaPay service, it means that you agree with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this policy, you can choose to not use FasaPay service. You are suggested to always read the Privacy Policy first as well as the  Terms and Conditions  of FasaPay before use the service provided on FasaPay application and/or website. 

**This Privacy Policy’s latest update is on 21st May 2018.**
